Hello everyone, in today's video
we will see how to get the benefit plan of Manu Life,
how to compare it, what are the
benefits and how much it costs,
how much is the monthly price of the plan, so
watch the entire video carefully.  Open the website,
BH Flights.com, then
click on these three lines.
After clicking on this,
Insurance is written here, click on it.
After clicking on Insurance,
scroll down to the bottom, then
see the Health and Dental Benefit Plans listed here.
After that, you will see the name of the company under the company name.
If you want to do GMS, click on GMS. If you want to do GMS,
click on GMS. If you want to
see the plan of GMS,
click on GMS.
After clicking on GMS, this page will open in front of you.
On this page, you will see Health and Dental
Insurance written here.  After that,
click on Learn More written as Learn More.
After clicking on Learn More,
all the plans will appear in front of you on this page.
So the first plan that will be the Association
Health and Dental Plan is this.
What is covered in this plan? It
covers medication, dental care
solutions, hospital and
ambulance services are also included in it.
This is for those of you who are self-
employed or part-time workers and
want to protect yourself.  So
what is the eligibility condition for this?
For this, you must have a health card.  So, no matter what
health and dental
plan, benefit plan, whatever you want to
take, the eligibility condition for each of you
is that you
must have a health card, then you can take it.
Next will be the one that Follow Me Health,
this is a very popular health plan of Menu Life.
Everyone gets it in it. Even if you have
health issues, you will get it.
Vision care is also included in it. It will have
extended health care.
Everything like massage etc. is included in it.
Its eligibility will be which you
can read here. So, its eligibility
came after that. Flexcare.
Flexcare is also one of their plans. Flexcare is a
little bit expansive but it has
coverage which is even more.
We will compare them once and then we will
write their recommendations and eligibility conditions.  The top of the line plan
that will be GI enhanced.  GI
is enhanced which these companies mostly give
if you work then companies
offer you this mostly they
offer GI enhance or they offer flex care
so you can see the details of the plan click on view
plan details
after that on this page we will
click on get quote
after clicking on get quote here
you accept it here all the
information you have to fill so
applicants are covered by government health this
means you also have a health card yes
this what is your province
click here
after that your date of birth date of birth date of birth fill
your date of birth select sex
after that if you
want to get coverage for family then
click on add dependent or if not click on cost
then you will know our price have a
look at this once  They have shown you 11 plans here. The
first plan is the one that costs
$9 per month. It will cost $99. There is
no medical in it. At the
time of application, 70% of
your medications will be covered. After that, in the
first year, you
can also get dental treatment done, which will cost $575.  Vision
50 dollars Vision for you every two years will get a
$5 million travel
insurance. This is a $5 million
travel insurance.
You can use it even if you are a truck driver
because you are covered for nine days between each trip.
If you want to see more details about this plan, you
can click on it to see more details.  So after that came the Combo
Plus Basic Plan. The coverage in it will be a
little more, like
70% of the medication in the first year,
which will reach $750,000 in the second year.
Dental was 500, 400 of it in the
first year and 800 in the next 60 years, then
750 every year.  The vision was 50 dollars in that one, it will
be 250 in this one.  And travel insurance
is the same.  After that, more plans came out,
so you can compare all the plans.
Now the Kobo Plus Enhanced Plan has arrived.  There is more
coverage in this,
look at the medication, you
can take medication worth $ 000, we have $ 00 in the first year, and
$ 000 in the second year, dental also
increases. How to buy any plan from it,
which you like,
read the details of the entire plan, it will be easy
for you. If we assume that
we want to buy Cobo Plus, then look at this, it is
$ 6, it also has the highest coverage.
Choose a combo plus plan and do it.
Click on the review code, then
after clicking on the review quote, here
they have given the complete details of the plan, what exactly is
included, by clicking here you
can read more about the plan, here you have to
fill your first name and last name information.
After that, click on Start Application Process.
You can purchase a policy by filling out your information here.  There is a
plan that you can follow.  So
many life plans are available to me.
My recommendation would be this, if we want to
compare all the plans, then you can
open this link on your laptop, then all the plans will be
compared well, then you
can choose the plan that suits you best.
If you want to make any modification in the plan, like
canceling it or getting any other add-on,
then you can contact me for that.
Look, my number is
written on Bahadur Singh's head, and my number is
on the hat on Manuel's website.  So
you can call me by clicking on this.
You
can connect with me on WhatsApp by going to H Flights, scrolling down to the bottom, and clicking on the WhatsApp button.  You can also get information about Easy Haiga plans,
compare them, and buy them if you want.  Please
share the video further.
Thank you. Have a nice day.